In this American English pronunciation video, we're going to compare the vowel and diphthong sounds of American English.
在这段美式英语发音视频中，我们将比较美式英语的元音和双元音发音。
You've already seen my set of 33 videos, The Sounds of American English.
你已经看过我制作的33个视频系列《美式英语的声音》。
In these videos, we went over the specifics of the mouth position for each sound, including all of the vowel and diphthong sounds in American English.
在这些视频中，我们详细讲解了每个音的口腔位置，包括美式英语中的所有元音和双元音。
In this video, we're going to do side-by-side comparisons of vowel and diphthong sounds that are similar.
在这段视频中，我们将并排比较相似的元音和双元音。
Seeing how similar sounds are different should help you solidify the individual sounds.
了解相似音的不同之处应该能帮助你巩固每个单独的音。
Let's get started.
让我们开始吧。
Notice how the lips are completely relaxed for AH, but the corners pull back and up for AH.
注意AH音时嘴唇是完全放松的，但AH音时嘴角会向后和向上拉。
Notice how there's more jaw drop for AH.
注意AH音时下巴的下垂更多。
Press your tongue down in the back for this vowel.
发这个元音时，把舌头的后部压下去。
AH UH Notice how the corners of the lips pull back and up just a bit for the AH vowel.
AH UH 注意AH元音时嘴角稍微向后和向上拉。
This is the word SAT.
这是单词SAT。
The lips are more relaxed for EH.
EH音时嘴唇更放松。
This is the word SAID.
这是单词SAID。
SAT SAID SAT SAID Notice how the lips are totally relaxed for AH, but flared a bit for AW.
SAT SAID SAT SAID 注意AH音时嘴唇完全放松，但AW音时稍微张开。
AH AH AH AH AH EH has more jaw drop.
AH AH AH AH AH EH音时下巴下垂更多。
The tongue arches closer to the roof of the mouth in EE.
EE音时舌头拱起更接近上颚。
EH EH EH EH EH EH EH has more jaw drop.
EH EH EH EH EH EH EH音时下巴下垂更多。
This is the word SAID in IH.
这是单词SAID中的IH音。
The front part of the tongue arches closer to the roof of the mouth.
舌头的前部拱起更接近上颚。
This is the word FIX.
这是单词FIX。
FIX FIX SAID FIX SAID The jaw drops less for EE.
FIX FIX SAID FIX SAID EE音时下巴下垂较少。
Here, EE is in the word PLEASE.
这里，EE音在单词PLEASE中。
Notice how much the jaw drops for the first sound of A.
注意A的第一个音时下巴下垂多少。
This is the word PAY.
这是单词PAY。
PAY PLEASE PAY PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE The jaw drops more for the first sound of the diphthong in the word PAY, but the tongue is forward for both sounds.
PAY PLEASE PAY PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE PAY这个双元音的第一个音下巴下垂更多，但舌头在两个音中都是向前的。
Here, the IH vowel is in the word FIX.
这里，IH元音在单词FIX中。
The second half of the diphthong is the same sound as the IH vowel, but here, the jaw drops a little less.
双元音的后半部分与IH元音相同，但这里下巴下垂稍微少一些。
PAY FIX PAY FIX The mouth position for the EH vowel in SAID looks identical to the first half of the diphthong in PAY.
PAY FIX PAY FIX SAID中的EH元音的口腔位置看起来与PAY的双元音的前半部分相同。
But look at the jaw for the second position of the AY diphthong.
但看看AY双元音的第二个位置的下巴。
Less jaw drop.
下巴下垂较少。
PAY SAID PAY SAID Notice how the lips and mouth are totally relaxed for the UH as in BUTTER vowel, but for the UR vowel, the lips flare and the tongue is pulled back.
PAY SAID PAY SAID 注意UH音（如BUTTER中的音）时嘴唇和口腔完全放松，但UR音时嘴唇张开，舌头向后拉。
UH URRR UH URRR There's more jaw drop for the UH as in BUTTER sound, which is usually stressed, than for the schwa, which is always unstressed.
UH URRR UH URRR UH音（如BUTTER中的音）通常是重读的，比总是非重读的schwa音下巴下垂更多。
Here, it looks like there's no jaw drop.
这里看起来没有下巴下垂。
UH The lips round much more for the OO vowel.
UH OO元音时嘴唇圆得多。
Flare them for the UH as in PUSH vowel.
UH音（如PUSH中的音）时嘴唇张开。
UH OOO The lips flare a bit for the UH as in PUSH vowel, but are totally relaxed for the UH as in BUTTER vowel.
UH OOO UH音（如PUSH中的音）时嘴唇稍微张开，但UH音（如BUTTER中的音）时完全放松。
UH UH UH Remember to start your lips in a relaxed position for OO.
UH UH UH 记得OO音时嘴唇要从放松的位置开始。
For the OH diphthong, the jaw drops a lot for the beginning sound.
OH双元音时下巴在开始音时下垂很多。
Tight circle for OO, and round, but not as much, for the second sound of OH.
OO音时嘴唇紧闭，OH的第二个音时圆，但不如OO音时圆。
OH The beginning position of OH looks a lot like the AH vowel, but the tongue pushes down in the back for the AH vowel.
OH OH的开始位置看起来很像AH元音，但AH元音时舌头在后部向下推。
The ending position of the OH diphthong has lip rounding, but the lips are always relaxed for the AH vowel.
OH双元音的结束位置有嘴唇圆形，但AH元音时嘴唇总是放松的。
OH AH OH AH Notice how the corners of the lips pull back for the first sound of the OW diphthong, but the lips flare for the AW vowel.
OH AH OH AH 注意OW双元音的第一个音时嘴角向后拉，但AW元音时嘴唇张开。
The jaw drops much less and the lips flare a little for the second half of the OW diphthong.
OW双元音的后半部分下巴下垂较少，嘴唇稍微张开。
The mouth position doesn't change for the AW vowel.
AW元音时口腔位置不变。
OW AW OW AW Now we'll see and say all those sounds and words again, mixed up in a different order.
OW AW OW AW 现在我们将再次看到并说出所有这些声音和单词，以不同的顺序混合。
Say them with me, in slow motion.
跟我一起慢速说出来。
AH AW AW AW AW AW AH SAT SAT SAID SAID UH UH UH UR UR UH UH UH UH UH UH SAT SAT SAID SAID AOOOAAAAAH AWWWWWW AWW pearls Iffffsh FYYYYthehhihhhifcs SSISE catтуut E I Pay Please Fix R Uh, ooh Uh, uh, oh, ooh This video is one of 36 in a new series, The Sounds of American English.
AH AW AW AW AW AW AH SAT SAT SAID SAID UH UH UH UR UR UH UH UH UH UH UH SAT SAT SAID SAID AOOOAAAAAH AWWWWWW AWW pearls Iffffsh FYYYYthehhihhhifcs SSISE catтуut E I Pay Please Fix R Uh, ooh Uh, uh, oh, ooh 这个视频是新系列《美式英语的声音》中的36个视频之一。
Videos in this set will be released here on YouTube twice a month, first and third Thursdays, in 2016 and 2017.
这个系列的视频将在2016年和2017年每月的第一个和第三个星期四在YouTube上发布。
But the whole set can be all yours right now.
但你现在就可以拥有整个系列。
The real value of these videos is watching them as a set, as a whole, to give your mind the time to take it all in and get the bigger picture.
这些视频的真正价值在于作为一个整体观看，给你的大脑时间去吸收所有内容并获得更大的图景。
Most of the materials you'll find elsewhere just teach the sounds on their own, in isolation.
你在其他地方找到的大多数材料只是单独教授这些声音。
It's a mistake to learn them this way.
以这种方式学习是一个错误。
We learn the sounds to speak words and sentences, not just sounds.
我们学习这些声音是为了说出单词和句子，而不仅仅是声音。
Move closer to fluency in spoken English.
更接近流利的英语口语。
Buy the video set today.
今天就购买视频系列。
Visit rachelsenglish.com slash sounds.
访问rachelsenglish.com/sounds。
Available as a DVD or digital download.
可作为DVD或数字下载。
My channel, where there are hundreds of great videos.
我的频道，有数百个精彩视频。
Don't forget to visit my website, where you can learn about my premium membership and online courses.
别忘了访问我的网站，在那里你可以了解我的高级会员和在线课程。